<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project_plan>
    <node title="VoiceFlow Project Plan" priority="high" status="pending" id="a1b2c3d4-e5f6-4a9b-8c7d-1e2f3a4b5c6d">
        <comment>This master plan outlines the comprehensive strategy for developing, launching, and scaling the VoiceFlow Project. This third revision adds further granularity, highlights dependencies, and integrates actionable metrics for a more robust and executable plan.</comment>
        
        <node title="Phase 1: Technical Development" priority="high" status="pending" id="e5f6g7h8-i9j0-4k1l-2m3n-4o5p6q7r8s9t">
            <comment>This phase focuses on building out the core application features, ensuring a robust and scalable technical foundation. The core transcription engine is complete, so the focus now shifts to user-facing features and infrastructure.</comment>
            
            <node title="Core Transcription Engine" priority="high" status="completed" id="b9c0d1e2-f3g4-4h5i-6j7k-8l9m0n1o2p3q">
                <comment>The initial MVP for browser-side transcription is complete and validated, using @xenova/transformers.js. This is a major milestone. The development server is running and the whisper-demo page is functional.</comment>
            </node>

            <node title="Feature Parity with Competitors" priority="high" status="pending" id="c8d9e0f1-a2b3-4c5d-6e7f-8g9h0i1j2k3l">
                <comment>To be competitive, we need to implement features offered by MacWhisper and Audio Note. This is critical for market acceptance and moving beyond the MVP. This work can be parallelized with Phase 2 activities.</comment>
                <node title="Advanced Export Functionality" priority="high" status="pending" id="l4m5n6o7-p8q9-4r0s-1t2u-3v4w5x6y7z8a">
                    <comment>Allow users to export transcripts in various formats. This is a key feature for professional users. A reusable export module should be created to easily add new formats in the future.</comment>
                    <node title="Implement Subtitle Export" priority="high" status="pending" id="r4s5t6u7-v8w9-4x0y-1z2a-3b4c5d6e7f8g">
                        <comment>Support for .srt and .vtt formats is standard and required by content creators (podcasters, video editors).</comment>
                    </node>
                    <node title="Implement Document Export" priority="medium" status="pending" id="u1v2w3x4-y5z6-4a7b-8c9d-0e1f2g3h4i5j">
                        <comment>Support for .txt, .pdf, and .docx formats for wider usability in business and academic contexts.</comment>
                    </node>
                </node>
                <node title="Transcript Interaction" priority="high" status="pending" id="i9j0k1l2-m3n4-4o5p-6q7r-8s9t0u1v2w3x">
                    <comment>Enhance the user's ability to work with the generated transcript, turning it from static text into a dynamic document. Performance with large transcripts (1+ hour) must be a consideration.</comment>
                    <node title="Implement Transcript Search" priority="high" status="pending" id="m3n4o5p6-q7r8-4s9t-0u1v-2w3x4y5z6a7b">
                        <comment>Allow users to search for specific words within the transcript, a fundamental feature for long audio files.</comment>
                    </node>
                    <node title="Implement In-Place Editing" priority="medium" status="pending" id="q7r8s9t0-u1v2-4w3x-4y5z-6a7b8c9d0e1f">
                        <comment>Allow users to correct transcription errors directly in the UI. This builds user trust and improves output quality.</comment>
                    </node>
                    <node title="Link Audio Playback to Transcript" priority="medium" status="pending" id="a2b3c4d5-e6f7-4g8h-9i0j-k1l2m3n4o5p6">
                        <comment>Clicking on a word in the transcript should jump to that point in the audio playback. This is a huge time-saver for verification.</comment>
                    </node>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Advanced Features &amp; Differentiators" priority="medium" status="pending" id="b3c4d5e6-f7g8-4h9i-0j1k-l2m3n4o5p6q7">
                <comment>Features that will set VoiceFlow Pro apart from the competition and create a strong value proposition. These should be prioritized based on feedback from user interviews.</comment>
                <node title="Real-time Transcription" priority="medium" status="pending" id="c4d5e6f7-g8h9-4i0j-1k2l-m3n4o5p6q7r8">
                    <comment>Transcribe audio from the microphone in real-time, providing instant feedback and notes.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="System Audio Transcription" priority="low" status="pending" id="d5e6f7g8-h9i0-4j1k-2l3m-n4o5p6q7r8s9">
                    <comment>RISK: This is technically complex and may require a separate desktop application. De-prioritized for initial launch but a key feature for a 'Pro' offering.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Speaker Diarization" priority="medium" status="pending" id="e6f7g8h9-i0j1-4k2l-3m4n-o5p6q7r8s9t0">
                    <comment>Identify and label different speakers in the transcript. This is a high-value feature for interviews, meetings, and podcasts.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Infrastructure &amp; Backend" priority="high" status="pending" id="f7g8h9i0-j1k2-4l3m-4n5o-p6q7r8s9t0u1">
                <comment>Ensure the backend services are ready for production, focusing on security, scalability, and user management. DEPENDENCY: This must be in place before paid launch.</comment>
                <node title="Setup User Authentication" priority="high" status="pending" id="g8h9i0j1-k2l3-4m4n-5o6p-q7r8s9t0u1v2">
                    <comment>Integrate Supabase for user login, registration, and management. This is a foundational step for a SaaS product.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Develop File Storage Solution" priority="high" status="pending" id="h9i0j1k2-l3m4-4n5o-6p7q-r8s9t0u1v2w3">
                    <comment>Implement secure, scalable storage for user audio files and transcripts, likely using Supabase Storage or a similar service.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Setup CI/CD Pipeline" priority="high" status="pending" id="i0j1k2l3-m4n5-4o6p-7q8r-s9t0u1v2w3x4">
                    <comment>Set up a continuous integration and deployment pipeline (e.g., using GitHub Actions) to automate testing and deployment to Vercel/AWS.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="User Onboarding &amp; Experience" priority="high" status="pending" id="a9b8c7d6-e5f4-3a2b-1c0d-9e8f7a6b5c4d">
                <comment>Create a seamless and welcoming experience for new users to drive activation and retention. A good onboarding flow is a feature in itself.</comment>
                <node title="Design Welcome Tour" priority="medium" status="pending" id="b8c7d6e5-f4a3-2b1c-0d9e-8f7a6b5c4d3e">
                    <comment>Create a short, interactive tour that highlights key features and helps users get their first transcription done quickly (the 'Aha!' moment).</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Implement Onboarding Checklist" priority="low" status="pending" id="c7d6e5f4-a3b2-1c0d-9e8f-7a6b5c4d3e2f">
                    <comment>A simple checklist to guide new users through essential setup steps (e.g., upload first file, try an export, invite a team member).</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Create Email Onboarding Sequence" priority="medium" status="pending" id="f4a3b2c1-d09e-8f7a-6b5c-4d3e2f1a0b9c">
                    <comment>Write a 5-7 email sequence to educate new users on features, provide tips, and keep them engaged during their first week.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>

        <node title="Phase 2: Business Foundation" priority="high" status="pending" id="j1k2l3m4-n5o6-4p7q-8r9s-t0u1v2w3x4y5">
            <comment>Establish the legal and financial structure of the business. This is a critical path to launch and can be done in parallel with technical development.</comment>
            
            <node title="Legal Foundation" priority="high" status="pending" id="k2l3m4n5-o6p7-4q8r-9s0t-u1v2w3x4y5z6">
                <comment>Draft and finalize all necessary legal documents to protect the business and its users. These must be easily accessible from the application footer.</comment>
                <node title="Draft Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy" priority="high" status="pending" id="l3m4n5o6-p7q8-4r9s-0t1u-v2w3x4y5z6a7">
                    <comment>Create comprehensive ToS and Privacy Policy documents, including GDPR/CCPA compliance clauses. Use templates and consult with a lawyer.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Draft License Agreement" priority="high" status="pending" id="m4n5o6p7-q8r9-4s0t-1u2v-w3x4y5z6a7b8">
                    <comment>Define licensing tiers (e.g., Individual, Team, Lifetime) and their terms of use.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Attorney Review" priority="high" status="pending" id="n5o6p7q8-r9s0-4t1u-2v3w-x4y5z6a7b8c9">
                    <comment>Have all legal documents reviewed by a qualified attorney specializing in software and SaaS. Do not skip this step.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Business Registration" priority="high" status="pending" id="o6p7q8r9-s0t1-4u2v-3w4x-y5z6a7b8c9d0">
                <comment>Officially register the business entity to operate legally.</comment>
                <node title="Form LLC" priority="high" status="pending" id="p7q8r9s0-t1u2-4v3w-4x5y-z6a7b8c9d0e1">
                    <comment>Register 'VoiceFlow Pro LLC' in the chosen jurisdiction and obtain an EIN from the IRS for tax purposes.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="File for Trademark" priority="medium" status="pending" id="q8r9s0t1-u2v3-4w4x-5y6z-a7b8c9d0e1f2">
                    <comment>Perform a trademark search and file an application for the 'VoiceFlow Pro' name and logo to protect the brand.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Payment &amp; Pricing" priority="high" status="pending" id="r9s0t1u2-v3w4-4x5y-6z7a-b8c9d0e1f2g3">
                <comment>Set up the system to process payments and define the pricing strategy. DEPENDENCY: User interviews should inform value-based pricing.</comment>
                <node title="Define Pricing Tiers" priority="high" status="pending" id="d6e5f4a3-b2c1-0d9e-8f7a-6b5c4d3e2f1a">
                    <comment>Finalize pricing for different tiers (e.g., Free, Pro, Teams) based on features, usage limits (e.g., transcription hours/month), and competitor analysis.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Configure Stripe Account" priority="high" status="pending" id="s0t1u2v3-w4x5-4y6z-7a8b-c9d0e1f2g3h4">
                    <comment>Set up Stripe, configure products/plans matching the pricing tiers, and integrate webhooks for subscription management.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Build Pricing &amp; Checkout UI" priority="high" status="pending" id="t1u2v3w4-x5y6-4z7a-8b9c-d0e1f2g3h4i5">
                    <comment>Develop the public pricing page and integrate the Stripe checkout flow into the application's subscription management area.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Implement Subscription Management UI" priority="high" status="pending" id="e5f4a3b2-c1d0-9e8f-7a6b-5c4d3e2f1a0b">
                    <comment>Create the in-app UI for users to view their current plan, upgrade, downgrade, cancel their subscription, and view invoice history.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Test Payment Flow End-to-End" priority="high" status="pending" id="u2v3w4x5-y6z7-4a8b-9c0d-e1f2g3h4i5j6">
                    <comment>Conduct thorough testing of the entire payment and subscription lifecycle (signup, upgrade, downgrade, cancellation, failed payments) using Stripe's test environment.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>

        <node title="Phase 3: Marketing &amp; Go-to-Market" priority="high" status="pending" id="v3w4x5y6-z7a8-4b9c-0d1e-f2g3h4i5j6k7">
            <comment>Prepare for launch and build a pipeline of potential customers. Marketing should start long before launch day.</comment>
            
            <node title="Branding &amp; Assets" priority="high" status="pending" id="w4x5y6z7-a8b9-4c0d-1e2f-g3h4i5j6k7l8">
                <comment>Develop a strong, professional brand identity that resonates with the target audience. DEPENDENCY: This should be done before the landing page is built.</comment>
                <node title="Design Logo and Visual Identity" priority="high" status="pending" id="x5y6z7a8-b9c0-4d1e-2f3g-h4i5j6k7l8m9">
                    <comment>Create the logo, define the color palette, and choose typography. This will inform all public-facing materials.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Pre-Launch Marketing" priority="high" status="pending" id="y6z7a8b9-c0d1-4e2f-3g4h-i5j6k7l8m9n0">
                <comment>Generate interest and leads before the product is live to ensure a successful launch.</comment>
                <node title="Develop Landing Page" priority="high" status="pending" id="z7a8b9c0-d1e2-4f3g-4h5i-j6k7l8m9n0o1">
                    <comment>Create a compelling landing page that clearly explains the value proposition and has a prominent call-to-action to join a waitlist.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Content Marketing" priority="medium" status="pending" id="a8b9c0d1-e2f3-4g4h-5i6j-k7l8m9n0o1p2">
                    <comment>Write blog posts and social media content about transcription, productivity, and use cases to attract the target audience and build SEO authority.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Build Waitlist" priority="high" status="pending" id="b2c1d09e-8f7a-6b5c-4d3e-2f1a0b9c8d7e">
                    <comment>Actively promote the landing page to build an email list of potential first users. GOAL: Aim for at least 500 sign-ups before launch day.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>

        <node title="Phase 4: User Feedback &amp; Validation" priority="high" status="pending" id="b9c0d1e2-f3g4-4h5i-6j7k-l8m9n0o1p2q3">
            <comment>Validate the product with real users to ensure it solves their problems effectively. This phase runs in parallel with development and is the most critical for de-risking the project.</comment>
            
            <node title="Customer Discovery" priority="high" status="pending" id="c0d1e2f3-g4h5-4i6j-7k8l-m9n0o1p2q3r4">
                <comment>Based on the 'Entrepreneurial Journey' coaching, this is a top priority. Get out of the building and talk to users to validate every assumption.</comment>
                <node title="Identify Target User Profiles" priority="high" status="pending" id="d1e2f3g4-h5i6-4j7k-8l9m-n0o1p2q3r4s5">
                    <comment>Define and document ideal customer profiles (e.g., podcasters, journalists, students, researchers) to focus interview and marketing efforts.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Conduct User Interviews" priority="high" status="pending" id="e2f3g4h5-i6j7-4k8l-9m0n-o1p2q3r4s5t6">
                    <comment>Schedule and conduct at least 20-30 interviews to deeply understand user pain points, existing workflows, and willingness to pay. Create an interview script to ensure consistent data collection.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Alpha &amp; Beta Testing" priority="high" status="pending" id="f3g4h5i6-j7k8-4l9m-0n1o-p2q3r4s5t6u7">
                <comment>Roll out the product to a limited audience to gather feedback, find bugs, and refine the user experience before public launch.</comment>
                <node title="Private Alpha Test" priority="high" status="pending" id="g4h5i6j7-k8l9-4m0n-1o2p-q3r4s5t6u7v8">
                    <comment>Invite a small group of 5-10 trusted users (identified during interviews) to test the initial product and provide detailed feedback. Offer them a lifetime deal for their contribution.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Public Beta Program" priority="high" status="pending" id="h5i6j7k8-l9m0-4n1o-2p3q-r4s5t6u7v8w9">
                    <comment>Open the beta to the pre-launch waitlist to test scalability, gather broader feedback, and generate early buzz. Define clear success metrics (e.g., 50% of beta users transcribe >3 files).</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Implement Feedback Loop" priority="high" status="pending" id="i6j7k8l9-m0n1-4o2p-3q4r-s5t6u7v8w9x0">
                    <comment>Set up a system (e.g., Discord, Canny.io) to collect, categorize, and prioritize user feedback systematically. Crucially, 'close the loop' by notifying users when their feedback is implemented.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>

        <node title="Phase 5: Official Launch &amp; Rollout" priority="high" status="pending" id="j7k8l9m0-n1o2-4p3q-4r5s-t6u7v8w9x0y1">
            <comment>The official public launch of VoiceFlow Pro. This is the culmination of all previous phases.</comment>
            
            <node title="Launch Preparation" priority="high" status="pending" id="k8l9m0n1-o2p3-4q4r-5s6t-u7v8w9x0y1z2">
                <comment>Final checks and preparations in the week leading up to the launch.</comment>
                <node title="Finalize Production Build" priority="high" status="pending" id="l9m0n1o2-p3q4-4r5s-6t7u-v8w9x0y1z2a3">
                    <comment>Incorporate critical feedback from beta testing, perform final QA, and freeze the code for the launch version.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Prepare Launch Marketing Campaign" priority="high" status="pending" id="m0n1o2p3-q4r5-4s6t-7u8v-w9x0y1z2a3b4">
                    <comment>Prepare emails for the waitlist (with a special launch day offer), social media announcements, and create a launch kit for Product Hunt or other platforms.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Launch Day" priority="high" status="pending" id="n1o2p3q4-r5s6-4t7u-8v9w-x0y1z2a3b4c5">
                <comment>Execute the launch plan with precision.</comment>
                <node title="Go Live" priority="high" status="pending" id="o2p3q4r5-s6t7-4u8v-9w0x-y1z2a3b4c5d6">
                    <comment>Deploy the application, enable public sign-ups, and switch payment processing to live mode.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Announce Launch on Key Channels" priority="high" status="pending" id="p3q4r5s6-t7u8-4v9w-0x1y-z2a3b4c5d6e7">
                    <comment>Send out all launch communications across all planned channels (Email, Twitter, LinkedIn, Product Hunt).</comment>
                </node>
            </node>

            <node title="Post-Launch" priority="high" status="pending" id="q4r5s6t7-u8v9-4w0x-1y2z-a3b4c5d6e7f8">
                <comment>The work doesn't stop at launch. Monitor, support, and iterate.</comment>
                <node title="Monitor System Performance &amp; Analytics" priority="high" status="pending" id="r5s6t7u8-v9w0-4x1y-2z3a-b4c5d6e7f8g9">
                    <comment>Closely watch server load, error rates (with Sentry), user sign-up funnels, and conversion rates (with Vercel Analytics/Plausible).</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Proactive Customer Support" priority="high" status="pending" id="s6t7u8v9-w0x1-4y2z-3a4b-c5d6e7f8g9h0">
                    <comment>Be ready to respond to user questions and issues promptly across all channels to build a reputation for excellent support. Create canned responses for common questions.</comment>
                </node>
                <node title="Plan V1.1 Roadmap" priority="medium" status="pending" id="t7u8v9w0-x1y2-4z3a-4b5c-d6e7f8g9h0i1">
                    <comment>Begin planning the next iteration of features based on post-launch feedback and initial usage data, focusing on quick wins and high-impact improvements.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
    </node>
</project_plan>
